{
    "subject": "Will_Self",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Deborah_Orr",
    "human_readable": "Will Self is married to Deborah Orr.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.984423816204071,
            "question": "Is Deborah Orr married to Will Self?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8867578506469727,
            "question": "Is Deborah Orr married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7293003797531128,
            "question": "Name the person Will Self is married to."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6819743514060974,
            "question": "Who is Will Self married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5387081503868103,
            "question": "To whom is Will Self legally bound in marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49107345938682556,
            "question": "What is the name of Will Self's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.484770804643631,
            "question": "What is the name of Will Self's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3892669677734375,
            "question": "Who shares a marital relationship with Will Self?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36848828196525574,
            "question": "Who is the spouse of the author Will Self?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3211508095264435,
            "question": "With whom did Will Self tie the knot?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Will Self is married to Deborah Orr.",
            "html": "yago_28218_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is the spouse of the author Will Self?",
            "html": "yago_28218_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who shares a marital relationship with Will Self?",
            "html": "yago_28218_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Will Self's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_28218_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28218_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28218_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28218_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28218_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28218_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28218_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28218_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28218_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28218_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28218_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Will Self is married to Deborah Orr\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while it is mentioned in the documents that Deborah Orr was married to Will Self, and also mentions their separation (e.g., \"The couple separated in 2017.\" in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_28218/re-ranker-msmarco/90.txt), it does not explicitly confirm that they were married at the time of evaluation."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Deborah Orr was married to the novelist Will Self, which supports the statement that Will Self is married to Deborah Orr."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information states that Deborah Orr was married to the novelist Will Self, but later on, it mentions \"Will Self\u2019s divorce from his newspaper columnist wife descended into a public spat yesterday when Deborah Orr identified herself as a victim of mental cruelty.\" This implies that Will Self and Deborah Orr were already divorced at some point before she wrote her book, indicating that they are not currently married.",
            "category": 0
        }
    }
}